Hey, you're early.
Agent Van Pelt reporting
for the night shift, Marshal Gorman.
At ease, Grace.
It's Witness Protection.
We're not invading Afghanistan.
Yeah, I know, but you know
what the rules say.
Thanks.
Anything I should know?
The Marshals Service
got an anonymous tip.
Somebody might be trying to make
a play on Justin tonight.
Something to it, you think?
There's always a threat, Grace.
That's how we gotta behave.
That's how we keep our guys alive.
- Hey, Grace. I thought that was you.
- Hey, Trina.
Um... I made this picture for you.
It's beautiful. Thank you, Trina.
I love those dogs.
Those are horses, Vic. Honestly.
Where's your dad?
Practicing his testimony
with Ms. Weymouth.
Let me tell ya, he's in a wicked
good mood tonight.
- Hey, Grace.
- Hi.
- Oh, welcome back, Big Red.
- Focus, Justin.
Mr. DeGeorge, a year ago
you witnessed someone
shoot Tanya Matthews in the head.
Could you please point out the man
who pulled the trigger?
Right there. Adrian Essex.
You are a money manager, correct?
And Mr. Essex was your client?
Yes, he was.
Six months ago,
you were arrested for tax fraud
weren't you, Mr. DeGeorge?
But the state offered you a deal.
Yes. In exchange for my testimony
against Essex
I don't go to jail.
Plus, my daughter and I get
Witness Protection.
Plus, we get to go over the same
thrilling questions
every single night.
All right. We're done for the night.
Me, too.
I'm off to watch the game
and kiss my dog.
Don't forget,
perimeter sweep, one hour.
Agent Van Pelt, the night shift
is officially yours.
"Dispatch here. Go ahead."
This is agent Van Pelt.
I need immediate assistance.
245 in progress
at my current location.
"10-4..."
Shots fired. I need backup. Now!
Justin?
Trina?
Oh, no.
- Anything on the girl?
- Not yet.
- We looking at a kidnapping?
- That or she just ran off.
- Where's the mother?
- Died last year.
It was just Trina and her dad.
All right. Put out an Amber alert
and a BOLO.
Already did. I've set up a perimeter
and notified C.H.P.
Good, and one more thing...
get that treated now.
That's an order.
We've got ten guys here
five more on their way.
- All right. Get going.
- Okay. You guys head that way.
That's...
That's it.
Table.
Barbecue.
- Jane?
- Horribly cold night tonight, Lisbon.
Do me a favor, would you?
Would you shine your flashlight
up into those treetops?
- Why?
- Because I like the effect
the way the light plays on the leaves.
The girl Trina
who made these drawings...
They're all from an aerial perspective
so my guess is, she has a spot up
high where she works
a place where she feels safe
and can hide.
- If she wasn't kidnapped.
- Kidnapping. Meh.
The man who'd pay her ransom
is lying in a pool of his own blood.
What do you know, huh?
I wonder why you doubt me, Lisbon.
Trina, are you there?
Sweetie, it's all right.
We're with the CBI.
I know it sounds made up, but we...
we have a web site and everything.
It's all right, Trina.
Just tell us what happened
from the start.
I know it's hard, but we really need
your help.
She can't do it, Lisbon.
She can't remember what happened.
Isn't that right, Trina?
It's all just mixed up.
Has anyone seen my dad?
Trina?
- Aunt Jodie!
- It's okay, baby. It's okay.
Hey. Bet you have a bad headache.
Yeah.
Well, that's gonna be a cool scar, though.
There is that.
Van Pelt, you okay? And Trina?
I'm fine. They took Trina to the hospital.
Damn it! I can't believe this.
- This where the son of a bitch got in?
- Well, it's gotta be, right?
The dead bolt's unlocked.
Unless Trina unlocked it
when she ran out.
She couldn't have.
The lock needs a key to get
in or out... this key.
- Did you forget to lock it, Grace?
- Hold on, Nicki.
Agent Van Pelt, when you did
your perimeter sweep
- did you lock that door?
- I-I was starting to
when I heard a noise
in the woods and I just, I think...
I don't know.
I can't remember if I locked it.
Okay. Damage control.
The guy you're looking for
is Adrian Essex.
Major drug trafficker.
We had an airtight murder case.
Victim was our main witness.
Essex will walk.
Well, that's a good motive.
We'll check it out.
"Oh, there you are."
I found a fascinating
clue. Ta-da!
- A matchbook.
- Yes.
The victim collected them
for some ungodly reason.
The question I have for you is why
is this matchbook all alone
and not in the bowl
with the rest of the collection?
Maybe Justin smoked.
No ashtray. No cigarettes.
No fumes of tobacco.
I'm leaving.
Wait! Don't touch that!
Forensics hasn't bagged it yet.
Did you know Nevada is both the marriage
and divorce capital of the nation?
They should put that on the license plate.
Yeah.
Where were you last night
at 10:00 P.M. Mr. Essex?
Your mother gave me a booty call.
Always happy to oblige the old girl.
She's not your type.
So you don't have an alibi then?
I gotta take a leak.
This stuff goes right through me.
DeGeorge isn't the first witness
against you to turn up dead.
- Two years ago, the Leland murder trial?
- How do you do that?
Maybe you got someone
feeding you information.
Just a lucky break.
The guy mixed with a bad set of people.
You do that, bad stuff happens.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Where were you last night?
Let me see. I don't rightly recall.
Maybe we should go help you
figure it out.
Against the wall.
Come on. Move.
Oh, yeah.
Ankle monitoring device.
I'm on home confinement during the trial.
Guess I have an alibi after all.
Yeah, seems like an excellent facility.
How's Trina doing?
Physically, she's all right.
Psychologically, it's tricky.
Tricky? Is that a diagnosis?
Trina's memory appears to be fine,
with one exception...
She still has no knowledge
of her father's death.
- You haven't told her yet?
- No.
No, and... and I'm not going to
un-until she's ready.
Until then, please leave her alone.
Ma'am, it's extremely important
that we speak to her.
- She may have witnessed the murder.
- Well, she definitely did.
She's blocking the memory,
because it's too painful.
I can help her remember.
I'll just put her in a light trance.
Hypnosis? Well, that's quackery.
- Well, then it can't hurt to try.
- No.
You're very confident
in what's right for Trina.
You yourself are a medical professional
of some sort.
A nurse, yes? Excellent posture.
I would venture you spent
some time in the armed forces.
- Navy?
- Army.
There's something more, though,
isn't there?
There's a deeper reason
you're so protective.
Trina's mother committed suicide
last year.
She was clinically depressed.
I'm really sorry, ma'am
but we have a job to do.
I'm not gonna tell her
that her father's dead, too
not until she's ready.
Excuse me, doc.
Where's the gift store?
I need to get some reading material
for the car ride home
and a peppermint bar.
I understand that
this is a difficult time for you.
If you just give us five minutes
with her, she'll be fine.
Look, I don't think
you're hearing me, agent.
- I don't think you're hearing me.
- Ladies...
Hey, Trina.
I brought you something.
Talent like yours deserves to be nurtured.
- Talent?
- Oh, come on.
I'm sure you've heard
that from your mom before.
I bet your mother taught you
to draw, right?
How did you know that?
Well, your father's a money manager,
pushes numbers around.
I figured that maybe your mom
is a little more artsy.
My mom was a really good artist.
She was the talented one
but she died.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
I have a question.
Your dad smoke?
- No.
- You sure? Interesting.
- Jane?
- Hey.
Are you trying to hypnotize her?
- Hypnotize me?
- I told you no!
The doctor said that her memory
will come back on its own in time!
Back off, tiger.
Easy, all right? I did no such thing.
Wait. Why would he wanna
hypnotize me?
Why won't anyone talk to me?
Aunt Jodie, where's my dad?
Trina...
He hasn't come to see me.
Where is he?
He's dead, isn't he?
Just tell me, please.
Yeah, that's right.
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
He was murdered last night.
Oh, honey. I'm sorry I didn't tell...
I know. It's okay.
It's okay.
Hi. I tried to find you this morning.
Yeah, I'm not really
in the mood for talking.
- I get it, but if you change your mind...
- Grace.
- Craig.
- Hey, I came as soon as I could.
You okay?
- I don't wanna talk about your feelings.
- Good. Me neither. What's up?
Adrian Essex has a number
one enforcer.
Eugene Boden, suspected
in a number of murders.
Essex can't leave the house, but
he can still order the hit. Let's go.
You're being too hard on yourself, okay?
The killer could've picked that lock.
I mean, he, he could've had a key,
for all you know.
Or he didn't need a key
because I maybe left it unlocked.
I lost a witness, Craig.
You're a great cop.
Hey, look at me.
I'm looking.
This will pass. I promise.
I'm interrupting.
Agent LaRoche of professional standards,
this is Craig O'Laughlin, FBI.
The P.S.U. Is looking
into last night's incident.
There are some... questions.
I've scheduled us to meet
this afternoon.
I will need your incident report
and a urine sample to screen
for drugs.
Agent Dubin here will escort you
to the restroom.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Uh, nice meeting you.
"Yeah, just a second.
Joey. Quick."
CBI, Mr. Boden. We need to talk
to you about Justin DeGeorge.
Yeah, I'm a bit busy right now.
You might wanna call my secretary
and make an appointment.
Let us in, sir. It'll just take a second.
I don't think so.
I already told you, I'm busy.
- Hey, let's not make this difficult.
- So piss off. Get out!
Police! Get on the ground now!
Everybody get down!
Get up.
Get on your knees.
I got it. Go.
"Police! Stop!"
Essex, stop!
Damn!
You look anxious.
Not at all.
No?
It would be understandable.
Agent Van Pelt...
did you leave that door unlocked?
I don't know.
That must be distressing, not knowing
if you're a good cop or not.
You remember Todd Johnson, don't you?
Cop killer murdered here
in our house by one of us.
Why?
I need assistance with my investigation
into his murder.
I need someone trustworthy.
Assistance?
- You have a whole unit.
- I need you.
Me?
Do you have a suspect?
Is it someone I work with?
We'll discuss the specifics
at a later point
but essentially all you would
have to do
is keep your eyes open
and at a later point
you might be asked to wear a wire.
You want me to spy
on my own department?
This is your chance
to redeem yourself, agent.
To prove you are a good cop
that you will take down a killer
no matter who it is.
And, of course
it would make my investigation
of your actions much easier
because a good cop
couldn't possibly have left
a door unlocked
and let a witness be killed
in front of his own daughter.
Am I right?
Are you threatening me?
I'm presenting you
with options, agent.
Take some time and mull them over.
Your boss is smart.
Essex had this phone rewired
to have the same signal
as the ankle monitor.
Turn the phone on, leave it at home
everybody thinks you're still there.
But Essex forgot one thing...
his neighbor's security cam.
Essex also left his house
the night of DeGeorge's murder.
It makes him look pretty good
for it, don't you think?
Lovely. So I guess I can go then.
I think he's forgetting
that he tried to buy
20 pounds of meth
from the Connera family.
Must be. What kinda price tag
does that carry?
20 years.
Won't be too bad.
I hear they're getting HBO in Folsom.
- Get to the point, Mary.
- You and Essex, you came up together.
You've been pulling jobs
with him for the last ten years.
You know where he hides.
You give us Essex, we can deal.
It doesn't have to be 20 years.
Tell me more about that... HBO.
Hospital? Why would you say that?
No, I know Aunt Jodie
had banned me from the hospital.
Quite militaristic of her,
don't you think?
Oh. Gotta run. Gotta run.
You're not welcome
at this hospital, Mr. Jane.
That's why I thought I'd find you
out here
amongst your, uh, puffing people.
You're trying so hard to quit smoking.
You bite your nails, and you smell
of hand sanitizer
but you are trying to quit for Trina
which I think is admirable.
What do you want?
You are not hypnotizing my niece.
No, no, no. No need to worry
about that.
I'm just going down
through the suspect list
starting with "A" for "Aunt Jodie".
You think I killed Justin...
You've gotta be kidding me.
No.
You're self-possessed.
You're strong-willed.
You believe that violence
can solve problems...
That's the army thing.
I'm a soldier, so I killed him?
Well, you despised him.
You had zero reaction to his death.
Forgive me for being more concerned
with the welfare of my niece.
Go ahead. Light up.
There's no judgment here.
Go on.
Why didn't you like him?
Justin beat my sister.
He'd get drunk and slap her around.
I was overseas.
I couldn't protect her.
So, yes, I did hate him.
When Molly...
when she died, I moved here.
I was going to fight him
for custody of Trina.
So there you go. Maybe I did
have motive for killing the bastard.
Nice lighter.
Your sister Molly...
where did you say she died?
A no-tell motel in Reno.
It's pathetic.
A hopeless place to kill yourself.
I was so angry at her for that.
I'm sorry, Jodie.
I seem to have misjudged you.
Please let me make amends.
Look at me.
Every time you breathe
a breath of that putrid smoke
remember this.
There's a fat, rich tobacco executive
thinking what a fool you are
every time you breathe that smoke
laughing at you
with his fat jowls wobbling
with glee.
- Do you see him?
- Yeah.
- Oh. Sorry. I didn't order that.
- No, I-I did.
Thank you.
It's your favorite.
Come on. And chocolate always makes
you feel better when you're upset.
Mm-hmm. I need to work
on my poker face, huh?
Yep.
I'm betting it's LaRoche.
Spill.
Pass that over here.
He wants me to spy
on my department
or he'll go after me.
Is this about that cop-killer murder?
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry, babe.
This is never fun.
But, look, someone in your organization
set a man on fire and let him burn alive.
Look, even if you knew who he was,
wouldn't you turn him in anyway?
Yeah, I guess I would.
Okay. Well, isn't that all
LaRoche is asking you to do?
- To catch the guy?
- Craig, these are my friends.
How am I supposed to wear
a wire while I talk to a friend?
They're your colleagues, okay?
I'm your friend.
I'm the one who's here for you
no matter what.
I get it.
It's a tough call.
Okay, so whatever you decide
just know that I love you
okay, and I'm behind you.
Okay.
All right. Now have some chocolate.
E-s-s-e-x. Adrian Essex.
Yes, that's the guy.
Let me know if you get a hit.
Is that the Justin DeGeorge file?
Yeah, and guess what I found in it.
DeGeorge called the police last year
claimed that Trina's Aunt Jodie
attacked him.
Not surprising. He abused her sister.
Says who?
Records say nothing about that.
Well, that's records for you.
Oh, there's stuff in here
about Trina's mother. Excellent.
Any leads on Essex yet?
My CIs are all quiet as mice.
Rigsby's got squat.
C.H.P, Border patrols, airports...
they've all got pictures of the guy.
We've just gotta wait.
I'm also getting a warrant out
on Essex's finances.
If he paid for the hit on DeGeorge
then maybe we have a trail.
Did you know it used to be illegal
to celebrate Christmas in Boston?
Yeah. Pilgrims thought the whole
spectacle rather debauched.
Didn't know that.
Got something.
A list of every property Essex owns.
- Good place to start looking.
- Great.
I'll get my guys on it.
Should take a couple hours.
Oh, sounds a little tedious.
Do you mind if I take a peek?
If we can get Essex and Boden
in a lineup
then we'll see what's what
and who's the killer.
A lineup for who, Trina?
She can't remember anything.
Well, the doctor says certain
stimulus can jog memories.
That's great, but we don't have Essex.
Well, I've got 100 bucks
that says I can figure out
where Essex is in less than a minute.
Pass.
A minute from now.
- Can I get in on this?
- Oh, yeah. Come on, baby.
Up! Up! Listen to me, you ogre.
I ask only this... Follow my finger.
- What the hell?
- You're telling me where your boss hides.
- Oh, come on. Give me a break.
- Who doesn't like a break?
A nice cold beer after a long, hard day
put your feet up on the big, comfy sofa.
Relaxes you, soothes you.
A break is a good thing.
I'm... I'm done with this.
So am I. Splendid.
- Time?
- 27 seconds.
"And here we go."
You will find Essex at 9 Eagle Drive.
Come on. No way.
When I put my finger
over the correct address
Boden couldn't help but react.
His lips tightened.
His nostrils flared ever so slightly.
Classic tells.
I'll get S.W.A.T. ready.
- Wicked good job, if you're right.
- Thanks.
But I'm not paying up
until the guy's in cuffs.
Well, just so you know, I prefer cash.
You guys set?
Let's roll.
Go. Split. Three and three.
Freeze! CBI!
Move!
Damn.
Gun!
Move! Move! Get out of the way!
Damn it.
Drop it, Essex.
Do it now.
Hands on your head.
Let's go.
I wanna make our position clear
from the outset.
We are not interested in a plea.
My client is innocent of every charge.
That right?
Sure, Adrian had the ability
to leave his house
but in no way does that prove
that he killed Justin DeGeorge.
He snuck out the night of the murder.
My girlfriend hurt her back,
so I went to see her.
- She'll swear to it.
- Naturally.
There's also a drug charge.
20 pounds of meth in that house.
But Adrian wasn't in the same room
and Mr. Boden will testify
that my client
had no knowledge of the drugs.
Your client evaded arrest.
Only after the CBI agents
illegally forced their way in.
That was by the book.
That's debatable.
There were no drugs in plain sight
no exigent circumstances
to enter the home.
Trust me. I get much better evidence
thrown out every day
for a lot less.
We need to put Trina in front
of a lineup.
We've got both Boden and Essex
in custody.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
Please, ma'am.
What is he doing?
Could you please control your man?
Oh, believe me, she's tried.
I-I think a lineup
is a ridiculous waste of time.
- She doesn't remember anything.
- A lineup might jog her memory.
Hi, Trina. You wanna I.D.
your father's killer?
D-did you just ask her
to come down here?
This is... unconscionable.
On the contrary, it's totally conscionable.
We can conscion this very easily.
I'll do it.
No, honey.
Honey, I...
I'm not gonna let you become
a witness, okay?
I-I won't put you in danger.
We'll protect her.
Like you protected her father?
Go ahead. Tell your aunt.
It's my dad who died, not yours.
- If you won't let me do this
- Trina...
I'll never forgive you, I swear.
Fine.
Okay then.
All right. Bring 'em in.
Now remember, Trina,
you can see them
but they can't see you.
Turn to the right.
Now, turn to the left.
And face center.
Do any of them look familiar?
- I'm sorry.
- You don't have to be sorry.
You did the best you could.
Rigsby, you wanna get Jodie
started on the paperwork
so we can get Trina outta here?
- Paperwork?
- Yeah, you know, the, uh...
- Form Y2Ks and the, uh...
- The standard minor release forms.
- It shouldn't take long.
- Sure. Yeah. Uh, right this way.
Hey, honey.
I'll be back in a minute, okay?
Okay.
Whatever you're doing,
you're not doing it alone.
Such little faith.
You wanna catch your father's killer?
Let me help.
Okay.
All you have to do is trust me.
Can you do that?
- Finally.
- Yeah.
Oh. I'm sorry.
You used blue pen.
You have to kinda use black.
- They're real sticklers about this.
- You're kidding me.
Oh, Janet. Essex's bank records?
Thank you. Finally.
Rigsby, stand guard over Trina.
Nobody gets in or out of that room.
Wait a minute. What happened?
What's going on?
Trina remembered
what happened that night.
What the hell is he talking about?
I hypnotized your niece.
- You son of a bitch!
- Who's the killer?
She hasn't told us yet.
She's still piecing it together
in her mind.
It's a very complicated process
but we'll know who the killer
is soon enough.
How could you do this?
How could you let him?
We are gonna take her
to a safe place immediately.
I'll call my director.
Anything you want, you've got.
I've got a great Witsec
apartment downstate.
We can keep her there long-term.
How do you sleep at night?
Most nights I don't,
but I give you my word
I will not let anything bad
happen to Trina.
Yeah? You better hope you don't.
Yeah, everything's clear.
Trina's fast asleep.
No problem, boss.
- Freeze!
- Jesus!
- Drop the weapon, Gorman!
- You scared the crap outta me.
Get down on the ground.
What are you talking about?
I just came by to see
if, uh, Trina was okay.
Trina's safe elsewhere.
We know you came here
to kill her.
Are you outta your mind?
Essex hired you tonight,
like he hired you to kill her father.
You know me, Grace.
We've been working together for weeks.
- Give up the weapon now!
- Just, just wait a second.
Just hold on a second.
I did not kill Justin.
- Three, two, one...
- Okay! All right. Calm down.
I'm putting the gun down.
All right?
We found a key
in Gorman's apartment
to the dead bolt at Justin's house.
I didn't leave that door unlocked.
He did.
I am a good cop.
So it would seem.
The investigation
into your actions is over.
And as to the other matter,
I decline your offer.
I won't spy on my friends.
A killer works in the CBI.
Every day you pass
each other in the halls.
You share information.
You might well put your life
into this person's hands.
I find that bothersome
but you seem fine with it.
Are we done?
We are.
- Hey.
- I'm proud of you.
- Aw. Thanks.
So how about I take you to lunch?
I have something special planned.
- Yeah. All right.
- Yeah?
You paid Gorman to kill Justin
and when you realized
Trina could I. D. Gorman
you put a hit out on her, too.
Yeah, like you can prove that.
Did you get this from the girl?
Anything she says under hypnosis
is inadmissible.
Oh. Oh. No, no, no.
I never hypnotized Trina.
Much to the relief of her aunt, I must say
Trina never remembered anything.
I did it to lure Gorman out,
and it worked a treat.
And we do have the proof
and not just the bag of meth
we found at Gorman's
but also your bank records.
You paid Gorman 10 grand
for each hit.
Every time Gorman made a deposit
the same amount came out
of your account.
- What are the chances?
- In the six years Gorman worked for you
it looks like you commissioned
five murders.
It seems like we're gonna close
some open cases.
And I think he's gonna look great
in an orange jumpsuit.
So if the girl didn't say anything to you,
how did you get on to Gorman?
That lovely hockey Jersey.
You're from Boston.
Oh, come on.
It's wicked obvious.
Gorman's also from Boston.
You guys even grew up
on the same block.
Yeah. How do you like them apples?
Hey. Congratulations. I heard.
You did? Already?
Oh, the P.S.U. investigation.
Right.
- Sorry. I thought...
- Thought what?
I thought you heard my news already
and I really wanted to tell you myself.
Craig asked me to marry him,
and I said yes.
That's wonderful, Grace.
That's terrific news.
He's a great guy.
Thank you, Wayne.
I...
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hi. Thank you for coming.
I-I don't know what's wrong.
Not at all. I brought Lisbon along
on account of you don't trust me
despite the fact that I helped
her quit smoking.
Now that's gratitude.
- In there.
- No good deed goes unpunished.
You remember now, don't you?
Remember what?
It's okay. You can say.
You're safe here.
I remember what happened.
I did it.
It was me.
What is she talking about?
It was Trina who shot her father.
No. No. That Marshal shot Justin.
That's what you said.
Well, technically Gorman
was hired to kill Justin.
"He snuck onto the property
but he never got to the killing part."
"What?"
But Gorman's killed a lot of other
people so, meh, you know...
good riddance.
Essex didn't know
that Gorman had failed.
He paid him for the hit.
Exactly. That's why Gorman
came after Trina.
He couldn't very well explain to Essex
that he'd cheated him
because she was the killer.
Trina, why?
Justin murdered her mother.
It-it was suicide.
Justin got these from a bar in Reno...
where Molly died.
And according to his case file
he told police he had
never been to Reno.
"I was just looking for something
to light a candle when I..."
I found these.
"I-I don't get it, Dad.
You said you've never been there."
"Come here!"
"Give me that!"
"Your mother thought
she could leave me"
"and take you with her like..."
- "like I'm some kinda schmuck!"
- "Ow! Dad, you're hurting me!"
"I swear to God, you say one word"
"one word, you will end up
the same way."
"Are you gonna make me do that?"
"Answer me, girl!"
"Answer me! Answer me!"
- "Hey!"
- "Aah! Don't!"
I'm so sorry.
We need to talk. Now.
You knew. You knew the whole time.
Um... not the whole time, no.
Hang on. What are you doing?
I'm calling juvenile services.
I don't want them to take her
to county for booking.
Really? That's your plan for this girl?
- Jail?
- Give me the phone, Jane!
No, I can't.
She took somebody's life.
She confessed to a police officer.
For God sakes, Lisbon,
the girl's father was an abuser.
So was mine! I didn't shoot him!
It was self-defense.
Exactly. And if it was
self-defense, she'll be acquitted.
Oh, and the courts never get it wrong.
The system never chews people up.
We are the system, Jane.
We get it right most of the time.
Okay, so she's proven innocent.
How much time do you think
she's gonna spend in foster care?
Six months? A year?
- I don't know.
- It's all so unnecessary, isn't it?
'Cause Trina's aunt is a nurse.
Aunt Jodie can get her
the psychiatric help that she needs...
Help, not punishment.
We don't get to pick
who gets a pass and who doesn't.
- That is the job of the courts.
- Please.
And our job,
our job is to catch the killer.
What happens after that
is up to other good people
who are also doing the best job
they can.
Damn it. Why did she confess?
Because she's a good person.
We don't have to do this.
We can let her go just this once.
Just once.
"All right. Let's go, ladies."
Don't be scared.
What do we got?
It's okay, Teresa.
Ho, we're busy here, lady.
Keep up the good work.
Trina, we're gonna take you home.
You just witnessed a beautiful thing.